

CONTACT

- +971 50 420 0271
- ✓ Dylanvdm15209@gmail.com
- **P** Dubai

QUALIFICATIONS

- STCW'10 SYSA
- Superyacht Deckhand Course
- Power Boat Level 2 Licence (RYA)
- Tender Operators Licence (RYA)
- PWC Licence (Jet-ski) (RYA)
- VHF Radio (RYA)
- Radar (RYA)
- Food Safety
- Forebs Living '2023
- Digital Marketing '2021
- TEFL Professional Institute '2021

SKILLS

- Team work
- Creativity
- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving
- Hard Working
- Trustworthy
- Watersport
- Maintenance
- Wash Downs
- Customer Service
- Handling Lines and Tenders
- Attention to Detail
- Confident Tender Driver

LANGUAGES

- English
- Afrikaans
- Dutch (basic)

DYLAN VAN DER MERWE

ABOUT ME

I am a versatile professional with a background in 4+ years hospitality experience, supervisor and sales, now seeking to transition into a dynamic role as a deckhand. I am excited to bring my diverse skill set to the maritime industry. I am confident that my strong communication skills, attention to detail, and passion for delivering outstanding experiences will make me a valuable asset to any crew. I look forward to contributing to the efficient operation and safety of yacht as a dedicated deckhand.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUMEIRAH HOTEL GROUP / SHIMMERS RESTAURANT / SUPERVISOR

2022 - Present

Providing exceptional service with a personal touch. Detail-oriented Supervisor dedicated to creating memorable dining experiences through attentiveness and a friendly approach.

Stock control | Team rostering | Customer service | Micros POS | Payment Handling

GRINGO'S CANTINA / FLOOR MANAGER / BARTENDER

2021 - 2022

Dynamic duo dedicated to elevating the bar and floor experience. As a skilled bartender, I craft delightful drinks with flair. As a strategic floor manager, I orchestrate seamless service, ensuring every moment is a testament to excellence.

Team training | Stock control | Floor Planning |
Schedules | Bartender | Waiter | Opening & Closing

O IRONHOUSE SUPPLEMENTS / SALES MANAGER

2020 -2021

Driven sales professional with a passion for health and wellness. Formerly excelled at a supplement shop, where I expertly guided customers toward their fitness and health goals with product knowledge and exceptional service.

REFERENCES

Elmarco Stoman (SHIMMERS)

Restaurant General Manager +971 50 127 8791 Nadia Da Silva (GRINGO'S)

Restaurant Manager +27 82 343 5344